#### RESUME

Name: NG Tung Ching, Raphael Gender: Male

Date of Birth: 3 September 1988 Contact Number: 59137928

E-mail Address: raphaelng@ymail.com

Independent, self-motivated, conscientious and well-organized, professional with seven years' experience in a top-tier law firm and another leading professional firm. A flexible and dependable employee who brings in-depth knowledge in listed company matters and superb analytical skills to your company.

# **Working Experience**

5/2014 - Present Tricor Services Limited - Corporate Services Department

**Position: Supervisor** 

Current Salary: HK\$28,300 per month, with year-end bonus, medical insurance and

reimbursement of HKICS Membership fee

8/2010- 5/2014 Fair Wind Secretarial Services Ltd. (subsidiary of Woo Kwan Lee & Lo)

**Position: Company Secretarial Executive** 

# Current and past responsibilities:-

- Handling full range of company secretarial matters in relation to listed companies (Both Main Board and GEM Board issuers) and different types of companies incorporated in different jurisdictions independently
- Preparing annual and interim reports, announcements and circulars
- Organizing and attending board and general meetings
- Liaising with different professional parties (i.e. Stock Exchange, Legal Advisers, Compliance Mangers and Regulatory Authorities)
- Ensuring proper compliance with regulatory disclosure, reporting and statutory filing requirements
- Handling ad-hoc assignments (e.g. DI Forms, next day disclosures return, drafting different types of announcements and documents for listed company)

### **Education**

Expected	Manchester Metropolitan University (organized by HKU Space)
Graduation Date	Bachelor of Laws (LLB) (Part-time)
2019	
9/2011 - 5/2013	City University of Hong Kong
	Master of Science in Professional Accounting and Corporate Governance (Part-time)
9/2009 - 6/2010	The Open University of Hong Kong
	Bachelor of Business Administration in Corporate Administration (Full-time)
9/2006 - 6/2009	School of Continuing and Professional Studies The Chinese University of Hong Kong
	Higher Diploma in Business and Corporate Administration (Full-time)

# **Qualification** The Hong Kong Institute of Chartered Secretaries, Associate Member (PE)

**Language** Fluent in Chinese and English, Good in Mandarin

Skill Proficiency in PC knowledge of MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Chinese Word

Processing, CSA and View Point software

**Expected Salary** HK\$32,000 per month (negotiable), with year-end bonus

**Availability** One month notice